[teacher] Do you know
why you are all bad at math?
FINAL EXAM
IN 16 DAYS
It's because of reasoning.
You all just memorize,
without actually learning things.
Oh Beom-seok.
You're walking in at the end of class?
[Beom-seok] Sorry.
[grunts]
[teacher] Anyway, I want you all to take
time to think about why I said this today.
- Class President.
- [boy 1] Attention. Bow.
[class] Thank you.
[sighs]
Beom-seok.
Are you hungover?
[Jeong-chan] Beom-seok-a.
Are you okay?
[tense music playing]
[chuckles] Does it feel like
your head's gonna burst open?
[Beom-seok] Yeah, I feel so sick.
[Tae-hun grunts] Aah!
I don't remember what happened last night.
[Jeong-chan giggles]
[Tae-hun] Bro, you were
freaking hilarious yesterday.
Dude, and Yong-jin?
He totally slept with that noona.
- Are you serious?
- [Tae-hun] Yeah, you don't remember?
[Jeong-chan chuckles]
Yeah, you even paid for his motel.
- His motel?
- [both] Yeah.
- [Jeong-chan] Man, this dude.
- [Tae-hun] He legit doesn't remember.
[Jeong-chan] Let's go for a smoke.
Hey, thanks for the drinks.
[Tae-hun] Yeah, seriously.
I had a killer time yesterday.
[Jeong-chan] I thought you were…
["Hero" by Meego playing]
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
[Su-ho yawning]
- [boy 1] Give it to me later.
- [boy 2] I can't.
[Su-ho] Hey, what's our group number?
- Group six.
- Cool.
I call dibs on the end seat.
[groans and sighs]
[boys laughing and chatting]
Hey, is Oh Beom not at school yet?
- He's here.
- He is? Since when?
[Tae-hun] Hey, Beom-seok-a.
That noona was
mad groping your thigh yesterday.
[laughter]
- [Jeong-chan] Oh.
- [Tae-hun] Have you talked to her?
- [Su-ho] What the hell?
- You were rapping so much at karaoke.
- In English too.
- [Tae-hun] We were like, "What?"
You must've had a lot of anger to get out.
We should go again.
- [Jeong-chan] Yeah, without Yong-jin.
- [Tae-hun] Yeah.
You made everything happen,
but Yong-jin stole your thunder.
Uh-huh. Like, right…
Can we talk for a sec?
[Jeong-chan sighs]
[Si-eun] What's with you?
[Beom-seok] What about me?
Why won't you answer my calls?
What?
I didn't know you called.
What's going on?
Why are you suddenly friends with them?
Jeong-chan and Tae-hun?
[sighs]
That's none of your business.
You, me and Su-ho should talk things out.
[sighs] I have nothing to say.
[poignant music playing]
He's looked down on me
since the moment we met.
He's never even thought of me
as a friend to begin with.
He probably just thought of me
as his minion who just tags along.
[sighs]
- [Su-ho] Talking shit?
- [sighs]
You're really pathetic, you know that?
What are you gonna do about it?
[sighs]
[techno music playing]
[girls chant] Drink it all, drink it all!
[all] Whoo!
- [girl 1] Whoo, whoo!
- [girl 2] Wow, he's good.
- [girl 1] Ooh!
- [Jeong-chan] Ah!
- Got a bottle for me too?
- [girl 1] What's up?
[Yeong-bin] Oh Beom-seok.
It's been a while.
Yeah, it's been a while.
- Come, sit here.
- [Tae-hun] Over here, Beom-seok-a.
Oh Beom-seok's a friend,
from my old school.
His dad's Assemblyman Oh Jin-won.
- [girl 2] Who's that?
- [girl 3] You know, that assemblyman.
You know who that is.
- [girl 1] Oh, seriously? That's awesome!
- [girl 2] Wow.
[Yeong-bin] This is Seo-hyeon,
Ji-an, and Su-a.
Friends from my new school.
This is Kang Woo-yeong,
my friend who'll make it to UFC.
[Woo-yeong chuckles] Uh-huh.
- You know Physical Therapist Woo-yeong?
- What?
- Um, physical therapy?
- [Yeong-bin] Watch it later.
It's his channel where he spars with
these idiots who think they're strong.
Freaking hilarious.
Nice to meet ya.
Yeah, nice to meet you too.
[Yeong-bin] Oh, right.
You're not friends with
Si-eun and Su-ho anymore?
- Uh-huh.
- [Yeong-bin] What happened?
You guys were pretty tight.
Ahn Su-ho freaking thinks
he's, like, king of the world.
Ahn Su-ho's so full of himself.
He thinks everyone is beneath him.
I need to kick his fucking ass someday.
Whatever.
I'm sorry about before.
Let's make a toast.
[Tae-hun] Bottoms up!
[all] Cheers!
[girls] Whoo!
[Jeong-chan] I wanna transfer schools too.
[Tae-hun chuckles]
[Seo-hyeon giggles] Isn't he your type?
[teacher] "Some experts…"
A few select specialists.
"…estimated…"
They guessed and approximated something.
DAESUNG ACADEMY
[Su-ho] Hey, Si-eun-ssi!
[sighs]
Aah. Ah.
- What's up?
- [Su-ho] What do you think?
It's Friday night.
Let's go drive around tonight.
Hmm? Hop on.
Cute. Mm-hmm.
[quirky music playing]
[motorcycle engine starts]
[Su-ho sighs]
Aah.
Unit 909. Mmm. Think of this as part
of your training and go take the stairs.
- You're making me work?
- Bro, I wouldn't do that.
I'm just trying to help you
get in shape, that's all.
- [starts engine]
- I gotta make a stop over there.
[Su-ho] Hey, cheers.
[groans] It's good, right?
[Si-eun] Aah…
[Su-ho chuckles]
Aah.
Oh, yeah. Is Yeong-i doing good at work?
Yeah. She's actually
pretty good at it, man.
She's great with the customers.
[joints crack]
[sighs]
It seems like…
Jeong-chan and Tae-hun are taking
advantage of Beom-seok.
[Su-ho sniffles]
And?
I think he's been buying them
clothes and shoes too.
And they've been saying
he pays for all the drinks.
And he's been reeking of alcohol.
What if Oh Beom's taking
advantage of them?
I think
that's what that guy's been wanting
from the beginning.
He first latched onto me and you
because he wanted to be popular.
He built up some cred hanging out with us.
[sighs]
You really think that?
[grunts]
[sighs]
[laughter]
- [boy 1] You guys have fun this weekend?
- Yeong-bin brought some pretty girls.
- You freaking traitors.
- [boy 2] Hey.
- What about us?
- I'm gonna date her.
[boy 2] Seriously?
Stop living in your imagination,
you idiot.
It's true love.
And she looks at me in a certain way.
She can't believe
you're a high school kid.
You look like an elementary kid.
- [boy 1] Fight him!
- Let's fight.
Hey, come and get it.
Seo-hyeon's been keeping in touch with me.
- Get outta here.
- [boy 1] Who?
Yeah, fuckin' right!
- [boy 3] What's she look like?
- I'm serious. We're DMing.
- No way.
- She messaged me first and wants to meet.
- [Tae-hun] For real?
- Mm-hmm.
- [boy 2] Yeah, right.
- [boy 1] What about us?
- [boy 3] Me too.
- Everyone except you. [laughs]
- I believe you!
- [Tae-hun] Ask her to bring Su-a.
- All right.
- I wanna come too!
- I'll DM her.
- I like Ji-an. No, wait.
- Not Ji-an.
- Tell her about us too.
- [Tae-hun] I want Su-a.
- Let's not be greedy.
- What about us?
- [boy 1] Her profile picture is hot!
- Come on, do it.
- [Tae-hun] Hurry.
- I'll message her later.
- [boy 2] Aw, man, just do it!
- [Tae-hun] I'm serious.
- [Jeong-chan] Beom-seok, you moving over?
- [boy 1] I'm drawing its head first.
- [Jeong-chan] Seriously, dude?
[boy 2] I can start drawing its body.
[tense music playing]
- [Tae-hun] Hurry up, dude.
- [Jeong-chan] Annoying.
[Beom-seok] Is it Su-a again?
- [Jeong-chan] Always.
- [Tae-hun] Please ask Su-a to come.
- [Jeong-chan] Isn't this seat great?
- [Beom-seok] Yeah, I love this seat.
[Jeong-chan scoffs]
A hundred million won per pyeong.
[sighs] You have to treat us big time.
- [Beom-seok] For sure, this weekend.
- [Tae-hun] Cool.
[Beom-seok] But not Tae-hun.
[Tae-hun] I'm not going, then.
[Jeong-chan] Hey, hey, guys.
We need to be a team.
Stop treating him like that.
What?
You're using Beom-seok.
- Ah, jeez.
- What the hell are you saying, dude?
School's turning into
a pretty scary place.
You've been making Beom-seok
pay for everything.
He's been buying your shoes and drinks.
This guy's fucking making us the bad guy.
Hey.
He offered to buy us all that stuff, dude.
I've made myself clear.
[Tae-hun sighs]
Hey, let's grab a bite.
Stop worrying about Beom-seok.
What?
You've done enough for that guy.
I think Beom-seok…
did all that because he's lonely.
I don't have the right words,
but that's how I feel.
[boy 1] Up for b-ball later?
- [Tae-hun] Nah.
- What's for lunch? I'm starving.
Man, gaenip? Fuck.
Who wants to help me unstick mine?
Hey.
Hey!
- Get in line.
- [boy 2] What are they doing?
You just cut.
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
[students gasping]
[boy 3] Oh my God!
[Su-ho] Get in line.
[clang]
- [clattering]
- [Su-ho] Damn it!
[boy 1] Come on. Let's get in line.
[sighs]
[sighs] I'm over this.
Get in line, Beom-seok-a.
[Beom-seok sighs]
No, thanks.
[students gasping]
That's enough.
[clattering]
[students murmuring]
[boy 4] Oh shit.
[boy 3] Oh my God.
- [boy 2] Did you see that?
- [boy 5] How is he taking them all on?
- How does he do that?
- [boy 2] What are they doing?
[boy 3] Oh shit.
- [Jeong-chan] Let's go.
- [Tae-hun] You okay, dude?
[Jeong-chan] Fuck that dude.
[music fades]
[Tae-hun] Fuck this, man.
That asshole thinks
everyone's freaking beneath him.
- Fuck.
- [boy 1 sighs]
[sighs] Hey.
Do you know anybody
who could kick his ass?
- What?
- [Beom-seok] I'll pay.
Do you know anybody
who could kill that asshole?
I do. Fuck!
- [Tae-hun] What?
- Woo-yeong.
Hey, I watched his videos.
He's a freakin' great fighter.
PHYSICAL THERAPIST WOO-YEONG
[Jeong-chan] Right?
This might fucking work. Huh?
[boy 1] He's strong.
[hits landing]
[Tae-hun] He throws good punches.
[Woo-yeong] How much will you pay?
[clears throat]
Would a million won be enough?
What day?
This coming Saturday.
It's Su-ho's birthday.
[Woo-yeong] Okay, sure.
I'll stream the whole thing live,
no edits.
- Where you going?
- To work out.
[Yeong-bin] That's dedication.
Wait a sec.
Didn't Woo-yeong get knocked out
by Su-ho before? In a tournament?
[Jeong-chan] That was forever ago.
That guy's still fighting,
but Su-ho's been hangin' out.
- Come on.
- [Yeong-bin] Hey.
Give him a handicap,
if you're so worried about it.
Am I wrong?
[all laugh]
Delivery!
[suspenseful music playing]
[clicking]
Hey, is this it?
[Jeong-chan] Yeah, I think so. Hold on.
- I'll do it. Fuck. Whatever.
- [Tae-hun] Can you hurry?
- [rattling]
- It's hard to cut off.
Darn it. Ugh.
Dang it. [grunts]
- [air hissing]
- [Jeong-chan grunts]
- Damn, I hope it's right.
- [Tae-hun] Ah, fuck.
What if he really dies?
[Jeong-chan] Then he fucking dies.
[clicking]
Oh, fuck.
- [clicking]
- Whoa.
- [tires screeching]
- [horns blaring]
[Su-ho] Whoa. Whoa!
- [horn beeping]
- [Su-ho] Move. Move!
[yelps]
[woman screams]
[onlookers gasping]
[man 1] Are you okay? Huh?
- Someone call an ambulance.
- She's calling them right now.
- Can you move?
- [woman 2] Do you know him?
[Yeong-bin] Hey, let's go.
Or else we'll seriously be fucked.
[tense music playing]
- [Jeong-chan] Hey, Beom-seok.
- [Tae-hun] Hey, hurry up.
- [man 1] You're okay?
- [Su-ho] I'm fine. I'm all right.
- [man 1] That's a relief.
- [man 2] Shouldn't he go see a doctor?
[music fades]
What did I tell you all
about "Cheongsan Byeolgok"?
Did you just get here?
[Su-ho] I'm sorry.
- [teacher] Eyes in front. Eyes in front!
- [Su-ho sighs]
[teacher] Let me break this down
for you one last time.
[sighs]
[teacher] It has a three-part harmony,
split into different verses with a chorus.
This is a song that represents
the universal characteristics
of Goryeo songs…
[teacher's voice fades]
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[boy 1] Hey, dude. Come on, let's go.
- What happened to your leg?
- It's no big deal. Hmm.
Hey.
Stop staring.
You disgust me.
Fuck off.
What's that?
It's nothing.
[Jeong-chan] Oh, fuck.
That legit scared me.
[Tae-hun] Do you think he knows it was us?
[Jeong-chan] No way. How would he know?
[Tae-hun] He doesn't, right?
Yeah, there's no way.
[Jeong-chan] So, Ahn Su-ho's
birthday is in two days?
[lively pop music playing]
[Yeong-i] Cool, I'm done.
Okay.
[sighs] Ahn Su-ho.
We'd be in Yangyang without that accident.
[sighs] Take some pictures.
Make me look pretty.
People will see this
and think it's your birthday.
Hurry up and take it.
[boy 1] Okay, and down.
Come on. One more. Hurry!
Good job.
[phone bleeps]
[ringing tone]
[ringing tone continues]
[typing]
Not answering?
[boy 1] Come on.
- No.
- [boy 1] Hold on for a second.
That bastard probably blocked your number.
Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
- [boy 2 grunts]
- [boy 1] Nice!
Cool, bro. Take five.
What is it?
[boy 1] Up, up. Come on!
- Nothing.
- [boy 1] Higher!
[Yeong-i] I mean, it'll take, like,
half an hour for Su-ho to get here.
Why are you making miyeok-guk already?
The longer it boils, the better it tastes.
[scoffs] Who told you that?
MY BUDDY SI-EUN, LOOK HERE
BEOM-SEOK: ARE YOU AT THE PARTY ROOM?
ARE YOU AT THE PARTY ROOM?
I'M NEARBY. CAN I SEE YOU A MINUTE?
Hey.
Aren't you guys not friends
with Beom-seok?
[Si-eun] Did Su-ho say that?
IT'S SU-HO'S BIRTHDAY TODAY.
No, he didn't.
Why do you ask about Beom-seok?
DON'T TELL SI-EUN OR SU-HO.
COME OUT FOR A MINUTE
SO I CAN GIVE YOU HIS PRESENT.
Huh? No reason.
Ah…
I'm gonna run to the convenience store.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[jazz playing]
[shop bell rings]
[Yeong-i] It's been a while.
You've been good?
[Beom-seok] Yeah, sure.
Hey, sorry about before.
I heard you got in trouble
'cause I answered your phone.
Si-eun's been really worried about you.
You should come to the party.
Su-ho's on his way there.
I'll help you two make up.
Hey.
First of all,
I wasn't in any trouble.
[tense music playing]
You'll help us make up?
[Yeong-i] Hmm?
I'm not interested
in making up with Su-ho.
[laughs]
[exhales]
- [Yeong-i] What the hell?
- [laughs]
[Su-ho] You can't go there.
[sighs] You're not supposed to plan
when you play. Hey, look, look.
Don't treat gaming like you're studying.
Okay?
Ugh. Give me that.
[sighs]
Anyway, is Yeong-i crawling
her way back? Huh?
What's taking her so long? I'm starving.
We can bring out the cake later.
Or should we just eat first?
Seriously?
That's a brilliant idea, bud.
Sounds like a plan.
Aah.
- I'll give Yeong-i a call.
- [Su-ho] Okay.
- [sighs]
- [dishes clattering]
[bleep]
The device is turned off.
- You will be redirected to voicemail…
- [Su-ho humming]
You know that cold pizza
tastes amazing when it's reheated?
You're in for a surprise.
You better be ready.
- [phone buzzes]
- [bleeping]
[microwave whirring]
[phone buzzes]
[microwave bleeps]
[dishes clink]
BEOM-SEOK:
18-3 BAMGOGAE-RO, GANGNAM, SEOUL
STOP IGNORING MY CALLS AND GET OVER HERE
[microwave whirring]
[suspenseful music playing]
Stop staring. You disgust me.
[microwave bleeps]
[Su-ho] Hey, don't bother
with Yeong-i right now.
Hey. Aren't you guys
not friends with Beom-seok?
I'm gonna run to the convenience store.
[Su-ho] Hey, come sit. Quick.
This smells amazing! Fuck, man.
YOUR BIRTHDAY PRESENT LOL
[Su-ho] Hey, this cheese is freaking…
Yes! [slurping]
Mmm.
The cheese!
You eat first.
Okay. Mmm.
Oh, I really wanna eat the fried chicken,
but I'll wait, okay? Aah!
ON MY WAY. WAIT FOR ME
DELETE 6 MESSAGES
BEOM-SEOK IS BLOCKED
SLIDE TO POWER OFF
- I have to run to the store real quick.
- [Su-ho] Right now? Hey.
Hurry up.
Five minutes is all you get. I mean it.
I'll be right back.
Go ahead and eat.
[door closes]
[Yeong-i sighs] I wanna smoke so bad.
[sighs]
Su-ho never even answered my calls.
I sent a photo of you,
and he's on his way.
[Yeong-i] Shut your mouth.
Your breath smells like shit.
[Yeong-bin laughs]
Hey, I've got a question for ya.
Are you and Ahn Su-ho dating?
[sighs] The hell are you on about?
It makes sense. Relationships are
a give-and-take sort of thing, right?
You didn't have a home,
so he let you crash at his place
and found you a part-time job.
[scoffs]
I want to know
what you gave him in return.
[Yeong-i] What a load of crap.
[ominous music playing]
[clattering]
[Si-eun] The Battle of Thermopylae.
Spartans were outnumbered,
so they fought in a narrow pass
to overcome their enemy.
In a one-against-many fight,
you must make good use of the terrain.
[Yeong-bin] What shall we get
to eat after this?
[Jeong-chan] I don't know.
Maybe jjajangmyeon?
[Tae-hun] Maybe jjamppong or jjajangmyeon.
[Yeong-bin] Jjamppong all the way.
[Tae-hun] I feel like
I'm kinda in the middle.
[Jeong-chan] Jjajangmyeon wins every time.
- [Tae-hun] It depends on my mood.
- [Yeong-bin] Always jjamppong.
What the hell?
- [Tae-hun] Look who showed.
- Si-eun-a.
[Jeong-chan] What?
- [boy 1] What the fuck?
- [Yeong-bin] Wow!
It's been
a fucking long time, Yeon Si-eun.
[Yeong-i] What happened? Where's Su-ho?
[Yeong-bin] It's so fucking nice
to see you.
- [Si-eun] Let's go.
- [Yeong-i] What? [gasps]
- [Tae-hun] Oh, fuck this! Fuck! Fuck!
- [Yeong-bin] Get them! Go!
What? Where's Ahn Su-ho?
[dramatic music playing]
[Yeong-i] Oh, shit! [sobs]
[Tae-hun] Fuck!
- [yells]
- [Yeong-i gasps]
- [Tae-hun groans] Fuck.
- [Si-eun] Get outta here!
- [groans]
- [clattering]
I'll get the police!
[boys grunting]
[Tae-hun] Son of a bitch.
[Yeong-bin] Hurry up and go!
- [boy 1] Fuck, dude.
- Get them, damn it!
Can you get here right away?
[whimpering] They're gonna
fuck us up really bad!
- [boy 1] Hey! Damn it. Shit!
- Yeah. They're coming after me right now!
- [boy 2] Stop, fucking asshole!
- [Tae-hun] Get him.
[Jeong-chan] Yeon Si-eun!
Damn it! [grunts]
Hey! Prick!
Hey!
- Oh shit!
- Oh shit.
[yelps]
This motherfucker.
[Si-eun panting]
Shithead.
[wrench clatters]
- [grunts]
- [Yeong-bin] What the fuck?
Fuck, man!
- [yelps]
- [crowbar clatters]
- [Yeong-bin groans]
- [paint can clatters]
Hey. Hey, wait a minute.
Wait.
Hey, wait a minute.
- Damn it.
- [Woo-yeong] Hey, looking great!
[sighs]
What's this about? Where's Ahn Su-ho?
[tense music playing]
Are you Yeong-bin's friend?
[Woo-yeong] A weapon won't help you much.
[Tae-hun] Oh shit!
[Si-eun grunting]
[coughs]
[gasps]
Using a weapon? You son of a bitch!
Ugh, what a little coward.
[Si-eun coughs]
[groans]
[Beom-seok] That's enough.
[music fades]
Let him leave.
What?
He has nothing to do with this.
I want Ahn Su-ho.
- Just let Si-eun leave.
- Sounds like a you problem.
I have something to settle with Si-eun.
Hey, I told you to fucking stop it.
This crazy fucking asshole.
Hey.
Yeah, what?
You son of a bitch.
We all came to help you.
Yeon Si-eun is your friend,
but we aren't?
[breathing shakily]
- I told you, didn't I?
- [Tae-hun] That's it.
[Yeong-bin] I told you,
just learn your place!
- You fucking bastard!
- [Jeong-chan] Ooh. I bet that stings.
- [Tae-hun chuckles]
- [Si-eun groans]
[melancholy music playing]
- [Jeong-chan] Kick his fucking ass.
- [Tae-hun] Go in hard!
[blows landing]
- [Jeong-chan] You missed a spot!
- [boy 1] You son of a bitch!
[laughter]
[breathing shakily]
[blows continue landing]
[laughter]
[Woo-yeong] Hey, Beom-seok.
Let's get another stream date set up.
[Tae-hun] Dang!
I told my hyeong-nims
I was fighting Ahn Su-ho.
Today was a little bonus. Hm?
I need to get paid.
- [whimpering]
- [Tae-hun] Fuck you.
[Jeong-chan] You must've thought
we were fucking idiots. Dick.
[Tae-hun] My chin still fucking hurts.
My chin. My chin! You shithead.
- Keep stomping on this spitball.
- Shithead! [yells]
You want some more?
[boy 1] Hey!
That fucking bitch called the cops.
- Hurry! Hey, hurry up!
- [Jeong-chan] Oh, fuck.
- Come on, let's go!
- [Tae-hun] Shit!
[boy 1] Hurry up!
[footsteps receding]
[music fades]
[Yeong-bin chuckles]
Hey, you thought you won, huh?
[laughs]
[sighs]
Hey, Yeon Si-eun.
Hey, Si-eun-a.
[poignant music playing]
[sighs]
[shudders]
[music fades]
["Self" by Meego playing]
♪ Swear to God… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Yeah, oh, we better watch out ♪
♪ We've nothing to lose ♪
♪ For myself ♪
♪ Yeah, right, for myself ♪
♪ Yeah, right, oh
We're on the point of giving ♪
♪ I still think we should stay here ♪
♪ Take my hand… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Yeah, we better watch out ♪
♪ We've nothing to lose ♪
♪ For myself ♪
♪ Yeah, right, for myself ♪
♪ Yeah, right, oh
We're on the point of giving ♪
♪ I still think we should stay here… ♪
ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND EVENTS
ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL
♪ If I could fix you, I wanna find ♪